

Daniel Dimitrov

Date of birth: 11/08/2000 | **Nationality:** Bulgarian | **Gender:** Male

Phone number: (+359) 887575828 (Mobile) | Email address:

ddimitrov1108@gmail.com | Website: https://dimitrovdev.vercel.app/ | Website:

https://github.com/ddimitrov1108 | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-dimitrov-94593a180/

Address: 8000, Burgas, Bulgaria (Home)

ABOUT ME

I am ambitious and motivated. I can work alone or in a team. I accept criticism and advice from more experienced colleagues in the environment in which I will be placed. I am ready for opportunities and challenges in an environment where innovation, education, and work are valued and encouraged.

WORK EXPERIENCE

27/03/2023 - 30/10/2023 Burgas, Bulgaria

X-RAY OPERATOR FRAPORT BULGARIA

08/04/2022 - 01/09/2022 Burgas, Bulgaria

X-RAY OPERATOR FRAPORT BULGARIA

06/2021 - 09/2021 Burgas, Bulgaria

X-RAY OPERATOR FRAPORT BULGARIA

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/2019 - CURRENT Varna, Bulgaria

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGIES Technical University of Varna

- Object-Oriented Programming
- · Synthesis and Analysis of Algorithms
- Databases
- Software Technologies
- Operating Systems
- Discrete Structures
- Web Design

09/2014 - 06/2019 Burgas, Bulgaria

SYSTEM PROGRAMMING Professional school of Chemical Technologies "Akad. N. D. Zelinsky"

DIGITAL SKILLS

Front-End technologies

NextJS (Basic) | ReactJS | JavaScript ES6+ | TailwindCSS | CSS3/SCSS | HTML5

Back-End technologies

MySQL | ExpressJS | Prisma | MongoDB

Others

C++ | C++ STL | Version Control System (Git)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **BULGARIAN**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B